[{"answer": "Yes, well, of course, I'm a Giants fan, being a New Yorker.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "I take it you enjoyed the Super Bowl yesterday?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, if you want to keep using that analogy to a fairly well, of course, Obama is sort of a New Yorker because he did time at Columbia.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Who do you think is going to win as things stand?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Do you see any other of the Republican candidates seriously threatening Romney at this stage?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "You know, according to all accounts, including people who are essentially friendly to him, he is a very reserved guy, whose main passions are his family and his Mormon faith, in which he's been very active not just as a parishioner but as a leader and lay official.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "What's the real man like?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, I think that Obama has been a very good steward and done all the things you said and managed the Libya situation, which he took a lot of heat from both the left and the right, quite well.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "What do you think as an overview about America's foreign policy going forward?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "I mean this election will be fought and won or lost on jobs and the economy, won't it?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "And final question, Frank, I men do you think that if Barack Obama wins the election, that if he gets to that point, he will be a better president in the second term than he's been in the first term?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I just hoped that it was an awful rumor.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about what had happened?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I had no doubt whatsoever but I don't believe he acted alone.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Have you ever had any doubt that Josh Powell was responsible for Susan's death?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "I do, because I know Josh and I know that he likes to make big grandiose plans and talk big but it always takes somebody else pushing him to carry things out.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "You think there's somebody else out there that was an accomplice?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I'm upset and I'm angry.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "And how do you feel about the fact that these boys, through a court ruling, had to be returned to him, given his obviously very confused state of mind?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "When they first moved to Utah about five years before she disappeared, they were pretty affectionate, they were still a kind of -- in the newlywed stage.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Or was there any sign that something awful would happen?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "And there was this bizarre twist where the father-in-law began to make all these claims about Susan being flirtatious with him and so on.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "He started to talk more and more to his father, Steve Powell, on the phone and to get more antagonist stick and controlling towards Susan?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I already knew it all because Susan had already told me many times over the years all about the fact that her father tried to hit on her, that he was obsessed with her, and that he was in love with her, that she couldn't stand him and that they moved to Utah to get away with him -- get away from him.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "What did you think when you heard all that?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "I do think so.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Do you think we ever will?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Everyone is in shock.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "What is the mood in the community?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "He and Josh were pretty good friends up until about a year or two before Susan disappeared.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "What's been his reaction to this shocking turn of events?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "I called Susan's father yesterday after a reporter told me what had happened or rumors what had happened.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Have you had any contact with the family?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "You are a Parisian?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "From France?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "I'm feeling quite good.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "How are you feeling?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Is Hollywood stampeding to your door?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "You know, I'm -- I'm OK.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "It doesn't get bigger, does it?", "qSentId": 347}, {"answer": "Not yet.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Have you prepared an Oscar winning speech?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "But what happens when a film becomes this huge, massive hit and you're all starting to think you may win an Oscar?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I really want to win, of course.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "You want to win, though, right?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "I have to be honest, I said, great.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "But when you first heard from Michel, I've got a great idea, I'm going to put you in a silent film -- be honest, what was your reaction?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Uhmm --", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Now, on the subject of love, one of my favorite questions I ask most of my guests -- and it's very appropriate in your case -- is how many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Let's just use your analogy, when the arrow goes into the heart.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Properly?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "To Michel?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "He's definitely the man of my life, yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "The love of your life?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "He's very smart and he doesn't take him seriously and that's all I love about him.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "What makes him so special?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "EJO: Yes.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "The dog?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "He doesn't really -- he's not a huge fan of dogs.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I mean, he loves the dog in the movie and he loves the character of the dog.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "So you make him have this dog that he just doesn't like?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yes, poor guy.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "So you've put this poor guy through hell?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "No, actually, it's the completion of a circle, because the first film I ever did was \"Murder By Death\" and I played a chauffeur.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "I mean, this is a bit of a downward grade here, isn't it?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No, because, actually, when you hear what it is, a silent movie, black and white, an unknown director, to us, two unknown French actors and you say, well, that sounds like a stupid idea.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Do you turn to your agent and manager and go, am I going crazy here?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Yes, sure he did.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Well, he saw the magic, didn't he?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I mean, certainly, yes, I could relate to it a bit.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "But for you, when you saw that narrative, how did it make you feel?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I mean, he's -- he's a big black no -- no especially elegant with a --", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "So he's a really offensive dog, as well?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "ORGAN: -- what about me asking you the same question I asked your wife, which is how many times have you been properly in love?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "She's really the -- the -- the -- the lead actress of my -- of my life.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "-- fall in love about every week, don't they?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I wouldn't think so.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Is it -- is it, in realism, going to actually produce a new birth to silent films or not?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "But I would do another silent film if Michel directed it.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Yes, because this silent film works because of his vision and his conception and his artistry, his mastery, his humanity.", "docId": "120206pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 626}]